<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="./css/xml.css" type="text/css"?>
<aaaa>
    <h1>
        Terms and Conditions
    </h1>
    <p>welcome to kwa jerry by viewing this page you agree to the following terms ! These <em>Terms and Conditions</em>  
    set forth the rules for your interaction with website www.kwajerryfastfood.co.za 
    (the "Website") run by [Company Name] (referred to as "us", "we", or "our").
    </p>
    <p>Please be inform by the terms and conditions for using the site.</p>

    <p1>
        1.Acceptance of terms
    </p1>
    <p>By using or visiting this website, you agree to these Terms. If you disagree with any portion of the terms, you are not allowed to use the website.
    </p>

    <p1>
        2.Change of terms
    </p1>
    <p>
        We retain the right to amend or update these Terms at any moment, in our sole discretion.
         It is your obligation to review these Terms from time to time for updates. If any modifications are posted to the Terms,
          your continuing use of the Website means you agree to such changes.
    </p>

    <p1>
        3.Privercy Policy
    </p1>
    <p>
        Our Privacy Policy also applies to how you use the website. Please go over our Privacy Policy,
         which also explains to users how we acquire their data and administers the Website.
    </p>

    <p1>
        4. Ordering and payments.
    </p1>
    <p>
    4.1 Order Acceptance: We reserve the right to accept or reject any orders submitted over the Website. For whatever reason,
     without informing you or anybody else, we have the right to reject or cancel any order, whether or not it has been confirmed.
</p>
<p>
4.2 Payment: All prices include relevant taxes and are shown in [Zar]. The payment options listed on the website must be used 
to make payments.
</p>
<p>
4.3 Delivery and Pickup: As mentioned on the website, we provide the delivery and pickup choices. Estimated delivery timeframes are
 not certain. Please bring a legitimate ID and your order confirmation when picking up.
</p>

    <p1>
        5. Refunds and Cancellations
    </p1>
    <p>
    5.1 Cancellations: Orders may be canceled up to [certain amount of time] after they are placed. After this time, cancellations 
    might not be accepted.

5.2 Refunds: Each refund is considered individually. Please get in touch with us at [Contact Information] as soon as possible after
 placing your order if you're not happy with it (specified time limits may apply).
 </p>

 <p1>6. Allergies and Dietary Requirements
 </p1>
 <p> It is your duty to check that the cuisine satisfies your dietary needs by looking over the contents stated on our menu.
  If you have any queries regarding ingredients or have any special dietary concerns, please contact us.
 </p>

 <p1>7. Intellectual Property
 </p1>
 <p>Kwa jerry and its licensors are the only owners of the Website and all of its unique content, features, and functionality.
  The Website is shielded by trademark, copyright, and other laws from both South Africa and other nations.
 </p>

 <p1>8. User Accounts
 </p1>
 <p>You are required to give us correct, full, and up-to-date information when you register an account with us.
  If you don't, you're in violation of the Terms and might have your account on our website immediately terminated.
 </p>

 <p1>9.Termination
 </p1>
 <p>Without warning or responsibility, we reserve the right to instantly discontinue or suspend your access to our 
 website for any reason, including, but not limited to, a violation of the Terms.
</p>

<p1> 10.Limitation of Liability</p1>
<p>If you access or use the Website, or are unable to do so, [Company Name], its directors, employees, partners,
 agents, suppliers, or affiliates shall not, under any circumstances, be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, 
 consequential, or punitive damages, including without limitation, loss of profits, data, use, goodwill, or other intangible losses.
</p>

<p1>11. Governing Law</p1>
<p>Without reference to its conflict of law provisions, of South Africa, laws shall govern and be construed in conformity with these Terms.
</p>

<p1>12. Dispute Resolution</p1>
<p>Arbitration will be used to settle any disagreement originating from or related to these Terms, including any inquiries about their existence,
 validity, or termination.
</p>

<p1>13. Contact Us</p1>
<p>Please get in touch with us if you have any issues regarding these Terms. 
</p>
</aaaa>